Minjun Kim

 ▮ 7788653349 | ■ minjunn.kim@mail.utoronto.ca | ☑ https://github.com/Minjun1Kim | ऻ linkedin.com/in/kimminjun/

Summary.

A University of Toronto undergraduate student in the Software Engineering Stream of the co-op Computer Science Program. Dedicated to creating revolutionary software with experience in full-stack web development, algorithms, and Object-Oriented Programming. Searching mostly for software and mobile application development positions, as well as teaching assistant positions.

Education

University of Toronto Toronto, ON

Co-op Computer Science Specialist | Software Engineering Stream

Sept 2021 - Current

• University of Toronto Scholar Award - \$7500

• Courses: Software Design, Software Tools and Systems Programming, Databases and Web Applications, Algorithms and Data Structures

Skills

Languages Java, C/C++, Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, SQL, LaTex, Markdown.

Tools/Frameworks Git, GitHub, Android Studio, Linux, Shell (Bash), JavaFX, React Native, Node.js, MatplotLib, GameMaker

Databases Firebase, MongoDB, SQLite, MySQL

Principles Algorithms and Data Structures, Complexity Analysis, OOP, Version Control, Agile Methodology, Concurrency

Experience

Math Peer Tutor

Port Coquitlam, BC

Terry Fox Secondary

Sep 2020 - Jun 2021

- Hired as a math tutor for pre-Calculus 12 and AP Calculus AB, helping students grasp difficult concepts and achieve exceptional grades in the AP exam both alongside the classroom teacher and through private tutoring sessions.
- Automated and optimised the grading and data handling process by SQL queries with Python to input and retrieve student grades and generate
 weekly performance graphs with Matplotlib.
- Technical Skills: SQL, SQLite, Python (Matplotlib), Java/HTML snippets, Google Sites

Teaching Assistant Coquitlam, BC

School District No. 43

Jul 2019 - Sep 2021

- Aided a classroom teacher with clerical tasks in a French immersion summer program, assisting a class of grade 2 and 3 students and guiding them in discovery and learning process.
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Led engaging classroom activities and built an enthralling interaction with each student}.$
- Soft Skills: Leadership, Communication, Organization skills.

Projects

ChatUofT Feb 2023 - Present

JavaScript, Node.js, React Native, HTML/CSS, MongoDB, Postman

- · A full-fledged application for a student communication platform developed by a group of frontend and backend developers.
- Implemented a graph search algorithm that recommends a user their most compatible individual on a biweekly basis based on similarities in their course schedules and interests.
- · Practiced agile software development methodology with daily scrum meetings upon assignments of user-stories.

System Monitoring and FD Tables Tool

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

C, Linux, Shell (Bash), Makefile

- Created a modular C program that monitors memory/cpu usage and running processes of the Operating System and displays corresponding graphical information and File Descriptor Tables.
- Utilised shell scripting and Makefile to automate build and execution processes.
- · Achieved the execution of multiple concurrent system queries through forks and pipes while intercepting signals from standard input.

Graffit May 2022 - Jun 2022

Graph Network, Data Structures and Algorithms, Queue, BFS, C

- Developed a mock-up social media platform utilizing C's graph network, managing 10k+ connections.
- Pioneered innovative feature that recommends potential new friends and brands through graph searches on the users' connections and interests

March 27, 2023 1